<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on JonTheNerd</title>
    <link>http://www.jonthenerd.com/categories/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on JonTheNerd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.jonthenerd.com/categories/linux/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kubuntu Notes</title>
      <link>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2021/11/13/kubuntu-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2021/11/13/kubuntu-notes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These are my notes while configuring Kubuntu 21.10 to my liking after first install. Mainly for my own future reference on other distribution installs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eeePC - not for the masses</title>
      <link>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2008/06/12/eeepc-not-for-the-masses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2008/06/12/eeepc-not-for-the-masses/</guid>
      <description>I managed to purchase one of these little gems in late April. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a longtime fan of Linux and Asus in general, so the thought of a little laptop running the free OS was enough to keep me dreaming until I broke down and ordered one. I bought a 7&amp;quot; model with the4 gig hard drive and an extra 2 gigs of ram. I did the ram install myself and setup the Advanced Desktop to my liking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Increasing the Wine font size</title>
      <link>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2007/02/04/increasing-the-wine-font-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2007/02/04/increasing-the-wine-font-size/</guid>
      <description>Thus far in using Ubuntu, I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to use only Linux applications. I&amp;rsquo;ll admit that some of them were just ports of their Windows or Mac OS X counterparts&amp;hellip;but I never had to install wine (a compatibility layer for running Windows programs). Well you know that torrent app I recommended? kTorrent? It&amp;rsquo;s crashed on me several times in the last couple days&amp;hellip;and ate up every bit of memory the system had this morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forced Enjoyment</title>
      <link>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2007/01/29/forced-enjoyment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2007/01/29/forced-enjoyment/</guid>
      <description>This isn&amp;rsquo;t the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve tried Ubuntu (or Linux for that matter). Several times in the past few years (since 2002 actually), I&amp;rsquo;d get the &amp;ldquo;Linux Bug&amp;rdquo; and repartition my hard drive to be able to try out some new distro. This would normally come about after I&amp;rsquo;d read some positive review of said distro (or from a friend). What have I tried in the past? I started out on Mandrake (now Mandriva), moved to SUSE 8 &amp;amp; 9, then MEPIS (great distro btw), and now Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The little Linux Box that could</title>
      <link>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2007/01/26/the-little-linux-box-that-could/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2007 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jonthenerd.com/2007/01/26/the-little-linux-box-that-could/</guid>
      <description>I decided that in order to tinker without disrupting the smooth operation of my workhorse PC, I ought to just build a testing box. In the event that I can actually tinker enough to stop wanting to tinker (like that&amp;rsquo;s going to happen), I also wanted the PC to serve a dual role as an eventual Media Center PC (Windows or otherwise). So I laid out some requirements:
 Multiple Core - I&amp;rsquo;ve read that the latest versions of software that play High-Def video (DVD &amp;amp; Blu-Ray) recommend having dual core.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
